Devin Veney

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

Contact(CLICK TO VIEW)







Skills

HTML5

Excellent

CSS3

Excellent

Adobe Suite

Excellent

JavaScript

Excellent

Mongodb

Excellent

Node.js

Excellent

Git

Excellent

React

Excellent

Next.js

Excellent

Ambitious Web Designer specializes in creating online destinations precisely tailored to each customer's needs. Translates vague design goals into actionable, technical details. Trusted provider of sites and online assets designed to drive return patronage and increase engagement.

Work History

2021-01 -Current

Full Stack Web Developer

Upwork

- Maintained complex technology infrastructure and collaborated with product team to implement new features and strategically plan for future products.
- Designed and developed efficient and maintainable software according to business objectives and needs of various clients.
- Consulted with engineering team members to determine system loads and develop improvement plans.
- Managed development milestones from initial steps through final delivery.

2020-06 -Current

Graphic/Freelance Web Designer

Fiverr, Henderson

- Worked with clients to gather and define requirements, establish scopes and managing project milestones.
- Designed website layouts, templates and unique branded looks.
- Put together videos for social media, advertising and informational purposes.
- Built corporate brands by designing cohesive looks between elements such as logos and letterheads.
- Created digital image files for use in digital and traditional printing methods.
- Met with customers to present mockups and collect information for adjustments.

Education

2016-08 -

Physics

2017-06

University of Nevada - Reno - Reynard, NV

2021-10 -Current

Japanese Studies

Akamonkai Japanese Language School - Nippori, Japan